hi guys I'm going to do a product review
and this time is for
skolan um 350 it's actually called um
Ultra trim 350 for skolan extract colus
forcolin root extract and it's 30
capsules this is what it looks like this
capsule it's a little red and gray
capsule I don't know if you can see that
or if you can see this
um this
here okay for
scen
okay yeah so this bottle here um was not
the bottle that was advertised in h Dr
Oz's uh television show he was actually
advertising a uh brown and yellow bottle
and it has had a lot of leaves on it you
know little herbs and um
on the YouTube video that I watched um
it says click on the link below you know
to get this product I clicked on that
link and I got some other bottle which I
tried I bought three bottles and it was
a ridiculous price but I did try it and
after you know using all three bottles I
think I lost one or two pounds something
very minimal um and everything was okay
that those three bottles I'm not talking
about this one so I did you know feel a
little better about myself it gave me
gave me a little bit of energy so I
thought well let me go ahead and and see
if I can find it again on the internet
and this time I found this one on the
internet and it w it also you know led
me to a YouTube video of Dr Oz on his
television show and it was the same
brown and yellow bottle and again it
said click on the link below I clicked
on it and this is what I got okay this
that's what they sent me this is
different from the other bottle I wish I
had kept that bottle so I could have
shown you I got so pissed off because
you know people keep getting ripped off
time and time again regarding this
product and I thought I'm going to do a
YouTube video but mine is going to be
honest okay I'm not going to sit there
and talk about how much weight I lost
and how fast it was and how wonderful
the miracle pill was I'm going to be
really honest with you so I tried this
so I took one this morning and I took
one a little while ago and just to let
you know the first one that I took I had
already eaten and about 5 or 10 minutes
later I had to go to the bathroom
immediately and I did um didn't do
anything to my stomach I didn't feel
sick or anything or any pain um but uh
I'm going to try it and I'm going to let
you guys know just because I'm really
tired of people just getting ripped off
let me let you know here this this is
what I look like today all right here's
the fat that I want to get rid of take a
look I've got back fat to got these
rolls that I want to get rid of and I
don't know if this is going to work but
like I said I'm going to be honest
because I'm tired of people getting
ripped off and I want to make sure that
um I give you an honest review and let
you know how it works and for this one I
bought three bottles as well and it was
another ridiculous price 100 and change
plus tax and shipping and uh on the back
of this thing here just so that you know
it says that it's a for skolen advanced
proprietary blend 500 Mig milligrams and
the proprietary blend contains for
skolan root extract but it doesn't tell
you how much and it says uh
laminaris laminar Flawless and caffeine
well you know what caffeine does to you
so I don't know I'm a little bit leery
about trying this but I'm going to try
it I'm going to try this one bottle and
I'll come uh I want you to come back and
and I'll let you know um the results
thanks for watching it's I really very
much appreciated and basically this is
for me and for you too so come on back
okay thanks bye